https://mycommunity.trentu.ca/privacy

Bookstore
Trent Forward: Learn more about our response to COVID-19.
PrivacyCollection Notice
Canada's Anti-Spam Legislation (CASL)
Best Practices for Protecting Personal Information When Using Email
Contact
TRENTU.CA / Access & Privacy / Privacy
Privacy
Privacy Protection
Trent University is committed to protecting personal information in its custody. This includes the personal records of students, alumni, employees, volunteers, donors and members of the public.
In accordance with current privacy legislation, departments at Trent collect only personal information that is necessary to operate their programs, services and activities. Records are held and disposed of securely, and access is limited to those individuals who require the information to perform their duties for the University.
The University is required to inform individuals about how their information is used. Trent's general information collection notice and detailed policies on the management of student records are available in the »University calendar.
Records that are not subject to privacy legislation; for example, employment-related records, are protected through University policies and collective agreements.
For more information about the protection of your personal information, or if you have a privacy concern you wish to discuss, please contact Trent’s Access/Privacy Office at 748-1011 ext. 1387, or privacyinformation@trentu.ca.
Collection Notice
Trent University is dedicated to letting its students know that we protect their information.
Learn more about how Trent uses students' personal information.
Collection Notice
Canada's Anti-Spam Legislation (CASL)
Learn more about Trent University's practices and how it complies with Canada's Anti-Spam Legislation.
Canada's Anti-Spam Legislation (CASL)
Privacy
Collection Notice
Canada's Anti-Spam Legislation (CASL)
Best Practices for Protecting Personal Information When Using Email
